Right now, Praew…
She’s in danger.
Praew!
She might be experiencing dissociation.
Even when she wakes up,
she might not remember some moments.
I looked through
the information of all four victims.
Their names are all
in the Thai Investment Bank case file
from 20 years ago.
You’re still the prime suspect.
(I’ve got all the chapters of Nekros.)
(Is it possible to meet you just once?)
(I’ll give you all the chapters.)
Mr. Thun.
Yes.
It’s me.
I’ll just be out with it…
I’m a big fan of Mr. Kill.
Thank you.
So you have all chapters of Nekros.
Yes.
I do.
And I’m more than willing
to give them all to you,
in exchange for an interview
as the creator of Nekros, though.
Okay, okay, okay.
I get it.
I’m asking for too much.
I know if you wanted to reveal yourself,
you would already have.
And I believe you have a good reason
for keeping your identity hidden.
But I want you to keep in mind
you won’t probably find
all chapters of Nekros again.
Do you think a fan like Asura
would keep them?
How’d you know about that?
Praew told me all about it.
She said there was a mysterious fan
sending you information for your manga.
I got so excited when I first heard it
and I was reminded of something.
Asura, in Japanese, means titans.
Titan, spelled in English, is Y-A-K.
When you think about it,
that’s K-A-Y backwards.
Isn’t that your name?
Maybe Asura is something you’ve created,
like a shadow following you.
You’re just never aware of it.
I have to go.
Maybe Asura is a shadow following you.
You’re just never aware of it.
(Do you still smell smoke, Kaye?)
Who are you?
The fire has gone out,
but the smell of smoke
and the burn on your skin
last longer, don’t they?
The most torturing part
is waking up to live your life
when you feel like a walking corpse,
forced to live among people,
forced to smile to the world,
when no one knows
you have nothing inside but ashes.
That’s the hardest part, isn’t it?
Just admit it.
You’re me.
And I’m you.
No, no, no.
You’re not me.
I’m not you.
I don’t want anyone dead.
Nekros was born from your grudge.
You feel satisfied every time
knowing all the victims whose death
you caused were in so much pain.
Am I right?
The screams of all those victims
sound like your voice calling for justice
you’ve been screaming.
Isn’t that how you feel?
No, no. You’re not me.
I’m not you.
Just admit it.
No, no.
Stop.
No. I’m not you.
I’ll never be you.
I know how you feel
because I feel it, too.
Stop talking.
Stop talking!
Stop freaking talking!
Shut up!
Shut up, asshole!
What the hell are you laughing at?
Shut up!
I’m not you!
You jerk!
Stop!
Listen up, Kaye.
Just let me out.
The world needs Nekros.
It needs us.
It needs someone
to get rid of those jerks,
those scumbags.
Just admit it, Kaye.
You feel just as satisfied as I do.
You’re me.
I’m you.
No one gets you like I do.
Am I right, Kaye?
PIMMA LIMKUNCHORN
Her condition is still troubling.
We must keep her closely monitored.
It’s been four days, doctor.
Prim!
-Ma’am, please step back.
-Prim, dear.
Prim!
Please wait outside, ma’am.
Patient!
-Patient!
-Prim!
Patient!
(I am a man of my word.)
THUN: I AM A MAN OF MY WORD.
PHAT: CAN WE MEET?
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
Sir.
Our target is on the move
and we’re right behind him.
How is Praew, Phat?
I heard from the doctors
that she’s conscious now.
Physically, she’s doing better.
But ever since she woke up,
all she does is stare into the distance.
She doesn’t talk
and doesn’t look at anyone.
I cleared up with the committee
about your behavior.
You can come back to work
whenever you’re ready.
Then…
Can I get reassigned on the Nekros case?
As a leader,
I don’t think turning back on my own words
would be a good look on me.
But don’t worry, Phat.
I’m sure a guy like Kitti knows
what he’s doing.
Right now there’s something
more important I need your help with.
In the next restructuring,
my name is on the list to be appointed
the new Commissioner-General.
Please let me know
if you need my help with anything.
I really believe you’ll improve our image
when you’re in office.
That is why I have to be extra careful
not to be involved with any misconduct.
Do you understand, Phat?
Yes, sir.
If you’ll excuse me…
Thanks.
Let me know
when Praew is out of the hospital.
Of course.
(Can we meet?
I have to talk to you about something.)
Follow me.
What happened?
I’m not sure about this but I feel like
I’ve been followed all morning.
I don’t know if they’re still trailing me.
But…
Here.
I got all chapters of Nekros.
Where did you get them?
I got them from Thun, the journalist.
He’s a former Nekros fan.
He downloaded all the chapters.
But Phat,
do you remember telling me
about how all the victims…
were somehow involved with
the Thai Investment Bank case?
Look.
This is Nekros’ victim in Chapter 25.
He’s the last victim
whose information I got from Asura.
I’m not responsible for this case anymore.
I’ll have the investigation team
retrieve this information from you.
Follow him.
I can guarantee Kaye
has nothing to do with the murderer.
And I’ve got all the rest
of the chapters of Nekros.
This is the information
on the victim in Chapter 25.
You should focus on
catching the real murderer,
and leave Kaye alone.
Did you know how Kaye was involved in
the Thai Investment Bank case?
Did you know what happened to his family?
You can’t deny the fact…
that Kaye has motivation
to take revenge on the victims.
And there’s a possibility
that Kaye is in fact a mastermind
pulling the strings on his followers.
You know I can’t help but think that you,
the son of the man
for whom his grudge must be the biggest,
might be one of the pawns
he’s manipulating,
without you realizing it.
Please don’t forget
that possibility, Inspector.
Dad?
Let me ask you something.
Putting up with this life
and working hard to pay for my treatment
to keep me alive today,
are you doing it because
you love me or because you hate me?
No, no, no.
No, Dad.
You hate me.
You hate me so much…
you think death would be too easy for me.
No.
No…
I’m someone who did you wrong,
who did your mother wrong.
Am I right?
No, no!
That is why you’re keeping me
caged in this rotting body!
You’re giving me hell on earth!
Why are you doing this to me?
No…
Hey, Nop.
(Inspector, we’ve just received
a report from Choti’s family)
(that he’s been missing
for almost three days now.)
I’m not your boss anymore.
(But, sir…)
I gave all the information
to Inspector Kitti.
(Understood, sir.)
But they don’t even understand
everything about this case.
Phat…
No one knows this case better than you.
Listen to me.
You said all the victims had something
to do with the Thai Investment Bank case.
The last jigsaw puzzle is
Choti Lertboriboon,
the accountant who faked the accounts
for Thai Investment.
He cooked the books
that were used in court,
allowing all the Thai Investment Bank
executives to walk free.
All my life,
I never trusted anyone.
You’re the only person I trust.
Maybe Asura is another victim
of this Thai Investment Bank case.
Asura…
is just like you, then?
Inspector Kitti can be trusted, you know?
Fine.
I get it now.
Since everything happened because of me,
I’ll be the one who ends it.
(Memorials of Evil.)
(What’s that?)
Memorials of Evil is a name used to mark
the locations where the bodies are found
in the Nekros manga.
These places are well thought out
and make sense for each victim.
CHOTI LERTBORIBOON
INVESTMENT SCAM EXPOSED
THAI INVESTMENT BANK EXECS
TO BE INVESTIGATED FOR FRAUD
Kaye, run.
Run, Kaye!
(The suspect is highly dangerous.)
(If he shows signs of resistance,
we’ll bring him in dead.)
He’s still here.
Search the place.
Don’t let him get away.
Yes, sir.
Let’s go.
This room.
This room is cleared.
No one’s here.
Go and check other rooms.
Yes, sir.
Kaye.
Kaye, look at me.
You’re safe now.
We’re at my place.
Calm down.
Listen to me.
I knew from the scene of the crime
that it wasn’t Nekros’ doing.
He set you up to take the blame
as the serial killer.
He’s writing the last scene with you
as the scapegoat.
Right now, you have to get it together.
Remember what you were doing there.
Tell me in chronological order.
Shit. Shit.
I…
I don’t remember anything.
Not at all.
It’s okay.
You don’t have to remember it now.
You can lay low here for a while.
You should clean up and get changed.
Take these.
I have to hurry back to investigate this.
If I was gone too long,
some cops might come looking around here.
But I’ll be right back.
Yeah.
Just… be careful.
I’ll keep this place locked.
Don’t open the door for anyone but me.
Hmm.
Take some rest.
I’ll find out who is behind this.
This looks like a set up.
Don’t you feel that it’s too easy?
Everything just falls into place.
I don’t “feel” it.
I follow the evidence.
And Kaye’s fingerprints
and the murder weapon
are found in the crime scene.
CHANKACHA’S HAIR IN THE CRIME SCENE
NO. 1 SUSPECT
“KAYE”
In all the cases before,
the murderer never left his prints
or any evidence.
I showed up at the scene very quickly.
He could have slipped up.
Stop protecting the murderer.
I’m not protecting the murderer.
I’m protecting what is right.
“What is right”?
You should listen to your uncle’s advice.
Don’t be too smart.
Because one misstep,
and you’ll lose your footing.
Just like your dad did.
Keep my father out of this.
Inspector.
Calm down, sir.
For your uncle’s sake,
I won’t hold it against you
for interfering with this investigation.
Please, Inspector.
I’d love to get back to work.
Keep your eye on him.
Don’t let him out of our sight.
Yes, sir.
MR. KILL IDENTITY REVEALED,
THE MAN BEHIND NEKROS
That’s perfect.
(I have to go.)
Actually… I agree.
I’ll give you an interview.
Shall we begin?
I promise to keep your face hidden
and I’ll do all the editing myself.
No one will get to see your face.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
We have with us here today
the creator of the manga
that sets the world on fire.
The manga that is the blueprint
for the vigilante murderer
who’s dealing with the people
the laws can’t touch.
Sitting with me here is Mr. Kill,
the creator of Nekros.
My first question is…
What was the inspiration for your manga?
The Nekros manga was inspired
by the Thai Investment Bank case.
Did you get all the documents?
Yes, sir.
Don’t make any mistakes.
This will affect how the case turns out.
Yes, Inspector.
My father was just a pawn
for the Thai Investment Bank.
He ended up being their scapegoat,
taking the blame for all the executives.
In this world,
justice has a cost.
My family…
We couldn’t afford it.
(The court has dismissed
the top management executives)
(in the Thai Investment Bank fraud case.)
(All suspects are proven innocent.)
(Another committee was set up
to investigate operational employees)
(for involvement with faking accounts.)
I didn’t do it!
(The laws require someone
to take responsibility.)
(And who’s a better scapegoat than
a nobody without a voice?)
I’m being framed!
I didn’t do it!
WE ARE SCAPEGOATS.
PLEASE GIVE US JUSTICE.
GIVE ME BACK MY MONEY
SCUM FAMILY
(The home that used to be my sanctuary)
(became a kind of Hell)
(that we had to put up with.)
(And our voices were too small
for the world to hear.)
Come on.
-Here it is.
-Dad.
(I still remember that day.)
(It was the first time in months)
(that I saw my parents smile.)
(The taste of that meal…)
(was the most delicious I ever tasted.)
(But at eight years old,)
(I was too stupid to understand)
(that those smiles didn’t come from joy.)
(Those were the smiles of someone
who gave up on everything.)
(What my parents did,)
(they didn’t do it out of hate.)
(They did it out of love.)
Dad!
Mom!
(They loved me so much they didn’t want me
to wake up in a shitty world like ours.)
Help me!
Dad!
Mom!
(The fire that day
burned my family to the ground.)
(But there was one thing it left behind:)
(a monster called Nekros.)
(For me…)
Nekros isn’t just art.
Nekros is a symbol.
A voice for the voiceless people.
It was the only thing
I could do at the time
as a response to this twisted world.
If you thought this was a fight,
why did you stop writing Nekros?
Was it because you accepted your fate,
accepted the truth,
or the fact that your family
deserved that punishment?
I’ll tell you what…
As a fan of yours,
I’d love to see you write Nekros again.
Phat.
I’ve been thinking about it all day.
But I can’t think of anything.
I can’t remember anything.
I don’t even know how I ended up there.
Did I kill them?
Am I a murderer?
Am I Nekros, Phat?
Did I kill those people, Phat?
Kaye.
Listen to me.
You helped me solve those murders.
You helped me save people.
You’re just a manga artist,
writing your pain down.
You didn’t mean for it to kill anyone.
You’re not a murderer.
Kaye.
Get it together, Kaye.
Get it together.
Kaye, you need to get it together.
Kaye.
If Inspector Phat insists on
taking the suspect’s side…
Inspector?
Then he’s obstructing our investigation.
I’ll find evidence to prove
that you’re innocent.
He’s a serial murderer.
We’ll take him in dead or alive.
Stop!
Come with me.
Thank you for not leaving me.
I told you I’d help you no matter what.